A Guide to the Rockefeller foundation records, projects, SG 1.16-1.19 (A90-A93) FA469
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A92), 1983-1989; 1.18; 42.93 Cubic Feet; 97 letter size document storage boxes (Boxes 1-97) 1 half letter size document storage box (Box 98)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - RF 86039 A148 - Greene, Linda S., 1986-1990 (Box 70, Folder 440)
      Study title: "Implications of Social Science Research for Employment Discrimination Law"
    - RF 86040 A1 - Desai, Ashok V., 1985-1989 (Box 70, Folder 441-442)
      Study title: "India and the Multinational Trade Negotiations"
    - RF 86040 A2 - Institute of Southeast Asian Studies, Singapore - Trade Policy, 1985-1989 (Box 71, Folder 443-444)
    - RF 86040 A3 - Korea Development Institute - "The New GATT Round Studies: Korea Project", 1985-1989 (Box 71, Folder 445)
    - RF 86040 A7 - El Colegio de Mexico - Trade Policy and Trade Negotiations in Mexico, 1985-1987, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 446)
    - RF 86042 - Institute of International Education - Developing International Relations Expertise in China, 1982-1992 (Box 71, Folder 447-448, Box 72, Folder 449-452)
      Formerly 155(601)
    - RF 86043 A39 - Suffolk University Law School - Work-Family Conflict, 1986-1990 (Box 72, Folder 453-454, Box 73, Folder 455)
      Study title: "The Work-Family Conflict: Restructuring the Workplace"
    - RF 86043 A40 - Wellesley College - Gender and Guilt, 1987-1990 (Box 73, Folder 456)
      Study title: "Gender and Guilt: A Study of Barriers to Social Change"
    - RF 86046 - National Conference on Social Welfare - Project on the Federal Social Role, 1984-1988 (Box 73, Folder 457-459)
    - RF 86046 - National Conference on Social Welfare - Project on the Federal Social Role: Supplementary Material (Box 74, Folder 460-464)
    - RF 86049 A10 - International Irrigation Management Institute, Sri Lanka - "Social Science Perspectives on Managing Agricultural Technology" Workshop, 1985-1990 (Box 74, Folder 465, Box 75, Folder 466-467)
    - RF 86049 A11 - Marcotte, Paul L., 1986-1990 (Box 75, Folder 468-471, Box 76, Folder 472)
      Grant jointly administered by Rockefeller Foundation and International Service for National Agricultural Research (ISNAR) for the purpose of identifying points of intervention in agricultural technology management systems, and in developing management tools for use in national agricultural research systems
    - RF 86049 A11 - Marcotte, Paul L., 1986-1990 (Box 75, Folder 468A)
    - RF 86049 A12 - Acheampong, Konadu, 1986-1990 (Box 76, Folder 473)
      Grant jointly administered by Rockefeller Foundation and International Fertilizer Development Center to research fertilizer investment for soil fertility restoration in West Africa
    - RF 86049 A12 - Acheampong, Konadu, 1986-1990 (Box 76, Folder 473A)
    - RF 86049 A13 - Watson, Greta A., 1986-1990, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 474)
      Grant jointly administered by Rockefeller Foundation and Centro Internacional de la Papa (CIP) to study the socioeconomic impact of the introduction of potato cultivation into warmer climatic zones in Asia
    - RF 86049 A13 - Watson, Greta A., 1986-1990, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 474A)
    - RF 86049 A15 - Carney, Judith A., 1986-1990 (Box 76, Folder 475, Box 77, Folder 476)
    - RF 86049 A15 - Carney, Judith A., 1986-1990 (Box 77, Folder 475A)
    - RF 86049 A16 - Ehui, Simeon Kacou, 1986-1992 (Box 77, Folder 477-478)
      Grant jointly administered by Rockefeller Foundation and International Institute of Tropical Agriculture (IITA) to research physical, biological, and socioeconomic processes in alley cropping systems for small African farmers
    - RF 86049 A16 - Ehui, Simeon Kacou, 1986-1992 (Box 77, Folder 477A)
    - RF 86058 A43 - Harvard University - Research on Engineering the Photosynthetic Apparatus of Rice, 1984-1989, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 479)
      Formerly 870
    - RF 86058 A52 - Max-Planck-Institute for Plant Breeding - Research on the Cell and Protoplast Culture of Rice, 1985-1989, 1996 (Box 77, Folder 480)
    - RF 86058 A54 - Purdue Research Foundation - Regeneration of Rice Plants from Callus, Cells and Protoplasts, 1984-1990, 1992, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 481-482)
    - RF 86060 A2 - International Food Policy Research Institute - Rice Supply and Demand, 1987-1990 (Box 78, Folder 483-484)
    - RF 86061 A4 - Kasetsart University, Bangkok - Differential Effects of Modern Rice Technology on Favorable and Unfavorable Production Environments, 1987-1990 (Box 78, Folder 485)
      Collaborative research project with Khon Kaen University, Thailand
    - RF 86061 A6 - International Food Policy Research Institute - Technological Progress in Chinese Rice Production, 1986-1990, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 486)
    - RF 86061 A8 - Cornell University - Hill Agriculture in Nepal, 1987-1991 (Box 79, Folder 487-488)
      Principal investigator: Dr. Krishna Belbase
    - RF 86061 A10 - Centre for Agro Economic Research (CAER) - Impacts of Modern Rice Technology in Indonesia, 1987-1989 (Box 79, Folder 489)
    - RF 86061 A11 - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) - Differential Impact of Modern Rice Technology in Bangladesh, 1987, 1989-1990 (Box 79, Folder 490)
    - RF 86063 A129 - Rockefeller University - Pharmacoparasitology Research Unit, 1977-1988 (Box 79, Folder 491-492, Box 80, Folder 493)
      Formerly 928
    - RF 86063 A129 - Rockefeller University - Pharmacoparasitology Research Unit: Supplementary Material (Box 80, Folder 494-495)
    - RF 86063 A130 - Affiliated Hospitals Center, Inc. (Brigham and Women's Hospital) - Immunoparasitology Division, 1977-1986, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 496-497, Box 81, Folder 498-499)
    - RF 86063 A130 - Affiliated Hospitals Center, Inc. (Brigham and Women's Hospital) - Immunoparasitology Division: Supplementary Material (Box 81, Folder 500-502)
    - RF 86063 A131 - Weizmann Institute of Science - Unit for Molecular Biology of Parasitic Diseases, 1978-1987 (Box 82, Folder 503-507)
    - RF 86063 A132 - University of Virginia - Division of Geographic Medicine, 1978-1988, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 508, Box 83, Folder 509-511)
    - RF 86063 A134 - Case Western Reserve University - Division of Geographic Medicine, 1973-1988 (Box 83, Folder 512-514, Box 84, Folder 515-516)
    - RF 86063 A134 - Case Western Reserve University - Division of Geographic Medicine: Supplementary Materiall (Box 84, Folder 517-518)
    - RF 86063 A135 - University of Washington - Geographic Medicine Unit, 1978-1988 (Box 84, Folder 519, Box 85, Folder 520-521)
    - RF 86063 A135 - University of Washington - Geographic Medicine Unit: Supplementary Material (Box 85, Folder 522-523)
    - RF 86063 A136 - Center for Research and Advanced Studies, National Polytechnic Institute - Pathogenesis of Invasive Infections, 1979-1988 (Box 85, Folder 524, Box 86, Folder 525-526)
      Centro de Investigacion y de Estudios Avanzados del I.P.N.
      Pathogenesis of invasive amebiasis, onchocerciasis, and American trypanosomiasis
    - RF 86063 A136 - Center for Research and Advanced Studies, National Polytechnic Institute - Pathogenesis of Invasive Infections: Supplementary Material (Box 86, Folder 527-529)
    - RF 86063 A137 - London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine - Department of Tropical Medicine, 1984-1987, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 530)
  - Arts and Humanities (AH)
    - AH 8713 - Rutgers University - Documentary Film on Anthropologist Margaret Mead, 1986-1991, 1995 (Box 87, Folder 531-532)
    - AH 8713 - Rutgers University - Documentary Film on Anthropologist Margaret Mead: "Margaret Mead: An Observer Observed", VHS (Box 3, Tape AV 12113)
    - AH 8809 - Music-Theatre Performing Group, Inc. - Intercultural Music Theater Works, 1985, 1987-1990 (Box 87, Folder 533-534)
    - AH 8814 - Nonprofit Video Publishing and Distribution Company - Feasibility Study, 1987-1989, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 535)
      Chief investigator: Herman E. Krawitz
    - AH 8815 - Teachers College, Columbia University - Federal Role in Education Over Next Decade, 1987-1990, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 536)
    - AH 8819 - Association of College, University and Community Arts Administrators, Inc. - Task Force on Presenting and Touring of Contemporary Artists, 1987-1992 (Box 88, Folder 537-541, Box 89, Folder 542-545)
    - AH 8819 - Association of College, University and Community Arts Administrators, Inc. - Task Force on Presenting and Touring of Contemporary Artists: Supplementary Material (Box 89, Folder 546, Box 90, Folder 547-549)
    - AH 8827 - American Council of Learned Societies - Archival Exchange Between the United States and the Soviet Union, 1985-1991 (Box 90, Folder 550-551, Box 91, Folder 552)
    - AH 8828 - Organization of American Historians - Magazine for History and Social Studies Teachers, 1984-1990 (Box 91, Folder 553-556)
    - AH 8828 - Organization of American Historians - Magazine for History and Social Studies Teachers: Supplementary Material (Box 92, Folder 557-558)
    - AH 8840 - Institute of International Education - Cultural Exchange Publication, 1986-1991 (Box 92, Folder 559-560)
    - AH 8842 - Modern Language Association of America - Foreign Language Instruction in the United States, 1987-1990, 1992-1993 (Box 92, Folder 561, Box 93, Folder 562-564)
    - AH 8842 - Modern Language Association of America - Foreign Language Instruction in the United States: Supplementary Material (Box 93, Folder 565)
    - AH 8852 - American Association of Museums - Museum Data Collection Program, 1988, 1990, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 566-567)
    - AH 8863 - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston - Artists of Argentina and Uruguay Exhibition, 1988-1990 (Box 94, Folder 568-570)
    - AH 8865 - Performing Arts Journal, Inc. - Interculturalism Publications, 1988-1992 (Box 94, Folder 571)
    - AH 8866 - University of California, Los Angeles - Chicano Art, 1986-1989, 1991 (Box 94, Folder 572, Box 95, Folder 573)
    - AH 8867 - University of Florida, Gainesville - History Teaching Alliance, 1987-1990, 1992 (Box 95, Folder 574-576)
    - AH 8873 - Institute of Contemporary Art, Boston - Latin American Art, 1988-1991 (Box 95, Folder 577)
    - AH 8875 - Smithsonian Institution - National Museum of African Art - Exhibition on Nomadic Architecture, 1987-1990 (Box 96, Folder 578)
    - AH 8883 - African Theatre Exchange (ATEX) - African Symposium Workshop in Mauritius, 1988-1991, 1994 (Box 96, Folder 579-580)
    - AH 8889 - (The) Mexican Museum, San Francisco - Mexican Folk Art Symposium, 1988-1992 (Box 96, Folder 581)
    - AH 8895 - Arts and Business Council, Inc. - Multicultural Arts Administration Internship Program, 1988-1990 (Box 96, Folder 582)
    - AH 880A - José Limón Dance Foundation, Inc. - Revival and Presentation of "Missa Brevis", 1988-1991, 1993 (Box 97, Folder 583)
      To be presented at the Festival del Centro Historico de la Ciudad de Mexico
    - AH 880C - WNYC Foundation - "Window on World Television", 1986-1990 (Box 97, Folder 584-585)
    - AH 880E - International Arts Relations, Inc. - David Avalos Exhibition, 1988-1990 (Box 97, Folder 586)
    - AH 880G - WGBH Educational Foundation, Boston - "New Television" Series, 1986-1989 (Box 97, Folder 587)
    - AH 880H - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (WNET), New York - "New Television" Series, 1986-1990 (Box 97, Folder 588, Box 98, Folder 589-590)
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A93), 1985-1993; 1.19; 121.03 Cubic Feet; 274 letter size document boxes and 1 legal size document box; Boxes 1-275
  Arranged by Program.
  - Arts and Humanities (AH)
    - AH 880I - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences (The Brooklyn Museum) - Conference and Programs Related to "Hispanic Arts in the United States" Exhibition, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - AH 880J - Dance Umbrella, Boston - Festivals/Residencies for "Tour de Fuerza" and "Africa Oye", 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
    - AH 8901 - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies, Inc. - Seminar on "Museums and Their Communities: Art, Ethnography and Interpretation", 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - AH 8902 - National Council for the Social Studies - National Commission, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5, Box 2, Folder 6-9)
    - AH 8903 - Social and Public Arts Resource Center - "Not Included" Exhibit, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - AH 8904 - Amigos del Museo del Barrio - Hispanic Art Exhibit, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      "Taller Alma Boricua: Reflecting on Twenty Years of the Puerto Rican Workshop, 1969-1989"
    - AH 8905 - American Dance Festival - South American Dance Week, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - AH 8907 - New School for Social Research - "Home: A Place in the World", 1988-1990, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - AH 8908 - United Latinos for the Arts in Los Angeles - Art Exhibition, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - AH 8910 - Joyce Theater Foundation - American Indian Dance Theatre, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - AH 8912 - Spoleto Festival U.S.A. - Tango/Orfeo Production, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      "Dangerous Games: Two Tango Pieces" (originally announced as Tango/Orfeo)
    - AH 8913 - Brooklyn Academy of Music - DANCEAFRICA National Tour, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - AH 8915 - Music-Theatre Group, Inc.- "Juan Darien" and New Projects, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - AH 8915 - Music-Theatre Group, Inc.- "Juan Darien" and New Projects (Box T5)
      Audio cassette – "Juan Darien", A Carnival Mass: 1. Tiger Tale; 2. Lacrymosa; 3. Gloria; 4. Trance; 5. Circus; 6. Lullabye; 7. Flower Cuttings; 8. Dies Irae; 9. Lacrymosa II; 10. Recordare. Copyright 1988. Music by Elliot Goldenthal. From a play by Julie Taymor and Elliot Goldenthal.
    - AH 8916 - British American Arts Association (US) Inc. - International Culture Relations Conference, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - AH 8918 - Trisha Brown Dance Company, Inc. - "Brown on Brown" Videotape, 1988-1991, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - AH 8920 - St. Ann Center for Restoration and the Arts, Inc. - "Brightness Falling" Theater Work, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - AH 8921 - District Curators, Inc. - "Long Tongues: A Saxophone Opera" Development and Production, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - AH 8922 - American Music Theater Festival, Inc. - "Latin Connection" Project, 1988-1992 (Box 4, Folder 23, Box 5, Folder 24)
    - AH 8930 - International Film Circuit - Touring Exhibition of International Film, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 25-26)
    - AH 8932 - American Symphony Orchestra League - Orchestra Library Information Service and New Music Project, 1984-1992 (Box 5, Folder 27-28, Box 6, Folder 29)
    - AH 8932 - American Symphony Orchestra League - Orchestra Library Information Service and New Music Project: Supplementary Material (Box 6, Folder 30-31)
    - AH 8935 - Exit Art, Inc. - Juan Sanchez Retrospective and Catalogue, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - AH 8938 - Cultural Research and Communication, Inc. - "Routes of Rhythm" Television Series, 1988-1990, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - AH 8939 - Musée National d'Art Moderne – "Magiciens de la Terre" Exhibition, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - AH 8940 - Asian Cultural Council - Museum Training as part of Festival of Indonesia, 1987-1989, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 35-36)
    - AH 8941 - WHYY, Inc., Philadelphia - INPUT 89 Conference, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - AH 8944 - Purchase College Foundation - Summerfare 1989, 1989-1990, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 38-39)
      State University of New York at Purchase
    - AH 8945 - La Napoule Art Foundation, Henry Clews Memorial - Third World Artists Residency Program, 1988-1990, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - AH 8948 - Sundance Institute for Film and Television - Latin American Filmmaker Exchange Program, 1987-1990 (Box 8, Folder 41-42)
    - AH 8949 - Association of American Universities - Coalition for the Advancement of Foreign Language and International Studies, 1986-1990 (Box 8, Folder 43-44)
    - AH 8955 - Institute of International Education - International Arts Exchange, 1988-1990 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - AH 8956 - American Forum, Inc. - Alliance for Education in Global and International Studies, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - AH 8957 - Bay Area Video Coalition, Inc. - "Art Video", an Anthology of the History of Video Art, 1988-1990, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - AH 8958 - Museum of Contemporary Hispanic Art, Friends of Puerto Rico, Inc. - "Contemporaries: Juxtaposing Perception" Exhibit, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - AH 8959 - Centre Africain d'Animation et d'Echanges Culturels, Senegal - "The Writer and Human Rights" Conference, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - AH 8960 - Visual Arts Research and Resource Center Relating to the Caribbean - Network of Cultural Centers of Color, 1989-1990, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      The Caribbean Cultural Center
    - AH 8961 - Brooklyn Academy of Music - 1989 New Music America Festival Presentation, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 51-52)
    - AH 8964 - Vivian Beaumont Theater, Inc. - Intercultural Theater Piece Entitled "Township Fever", 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - AH 8967 - Walker Art Center, Minneapolis - International Festival of Performing Arts, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - AH 8971 - Oxford University - Conference on Indian Policies, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - AH 8974 - International Film Seminars, Inc. - 35th Annual Robert Flaherty Seminar, 1989, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - AH 8975 - Bryn Mawr College, Pennsylvania - "Relativism and Objectivity: Perspectives on Third World Culture" Conference, 1989-1990, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - AH 8976 - Educational Broadcasting Corp. - "Channel Crossings" Television Series, 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 58-59, Box 11, Folder 60)
    - AH 8977 - Visual Arts Research and Resource Center Relating to the Caribbean, Inc. - Resource Center, 1985-1989, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 61-63)
    - AH 8978 - Yellow Rings Institute for Contemporary Studies and the Arts, Pennsylvania - International Residency Program, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - AH 8981- Crossroads, Inc. - Collaborative Cross-Cultural Theater Piece Entitled "Sheila's Day", 1989-1990, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 65)
      File Plan
      Crossroads Theatre Company, New Brunswick, New Jersey
    - AH 8982 - Arts Resources in Collaboration, Inc. - Restoration of "Eye on Dance" Programs, 1986-1987, 1989, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - AH 8983 - Dance USA - 1990 International Roundtable, 1984, 1987, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 67-68)
      Roundtable theme: "Internationalism in Dance: Past, Present and Future"
    - AH 8987 - Urban Bush Women, New York - New Works, Including "Praise House", 1988-1991 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - AH 8988 - Carver Development Board, Texas - African Caribbean Festival, 1989-1990, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 70-71)
    - AH 8993 - Mary McLeod Bethune Museum and Archives - Development Office, 1985-1990 (Box 13, Folder 72-76)
      Formerly EO 8601
    - AH 8993 - Mary McLeod Bethune Museum and Archives - Development Office: Supplementary Material (Box 13, Folder 77, Box 14, Folder 78)
    - AH 8994 - Corcoran Gallery of Art - "Facing History: The Black Image in American Art" Exhibit, 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 79-81)
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS)
    - AS 8701 - Biotechnology Career Fellowships (in Agricultural Sciences), 1985-1992 (Box 14, Folder 82, Box 15, Folder 83)
      Fellowship recipients: Timothy Uzochukwu Obi, Clement Kanyidinma Ojeh, Adelekan Oyejide
    - AS 8729 - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development - Comparative Analysis of Agricultural Development in Asia and Africa, 1986-1993 (Box 15, Folder 84-85)
    - AS 8805 - Academia Sinica, Beijing - "Genetic Manipulation in Crops" Newsletter, 1986-1989, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 86)
    - AS 8807 - Cornell University - Martin Isaac Meltzer, 1987-1993, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 87-88, Box 16, Folder 89)
      Dissertation: "Livestock Biotechnology: The Economic and Ecological Impact of Alternatives for Controlling Ticks and Tick-Borne Diseases in Africa", 1990
    - AS 8807 - Cornell University - Martin Isaac Meltzer, 1987-1993, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 87A)
    - AS 8814 - International Fund for Agricultural Research - Tropical Forests and Crop Genetic Resources Study, 1987-1991 (Box 16, Folder 90)
    - AS 8814 - International Fund for Agricultural Research - Tropical Forests and Crop Genetic Resources Study: Supplementary Material (Box 16, Folder 91, Box 17, Folder 92-96, Box 18, Folder 97)
    - AS 8826 - University of Botswana - Income and Employment Generation in Rural Botswana, 1988, 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 98)
    - AS 8831 - Vanderbilt University - Developing World Food Production, 1987-1993, 1996, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 99-101)
      Secondary grantee: James Lang
    - AS 8843 - (The) Panos Institute - Biotechnology and Sustainable Development Dossier, 1987-1990, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 102)
    - AS 8903 - American Agricultural Economics Association - Chinese Rural Development Symposium, 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 103)
    - AS 8904 - Fudan University, Shanghei - Fudan International Symposium on New Frontiers of Genetics, 1988-1989, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 104)
    - AS 8906 - International Food Policy Research Institute - Joint Study with Centro Internacional de Agricultura Tropical (CIAT) on the Humid Tropics, 1988-1991 (Box 19, Folder 105)
    - AS 8907 - Asian and Pacific Development Centre, Malaysia - Seminar on "Public Policy Implications of Biotechnology for Asian Agriculture", 1988-1991 (Box 19, Folder 106-107)
    - AS 8909 - World Bank - Evaluation of Non-Associated Centers by Consultative Group for International Agricultural Research (CGIAR), 1988-1989, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 108)
    - AS 8910 - International Council for Research in Agroforestry, Kenya - Review, 1988-1991 (Box 19, Folder 109)
    - AS 8911 - International Irrigation Management Institute - Program and Management Review, 1988-1990 (Box 20, Folder 110-111)
    - AS 8912 - Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maíz y Trigo (CIMMYT), Mexico - Impact of Technological Change on Wheat in Pakistan, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 112)
      International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center (CIMMYT)
      Joint project with Development Research and Management Services (DRMS), Pakistan
    - AS 8914 - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development - Sub-Saharan Graduate Students, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 113)
    - AS 8915 - Indian Environmental Society - Third International Conference on Environmental Education, 1988-1991 (Box 20, Folder 114)
    - AS 8916 - Townsend, Robert M., 1988-1991 (Box 20, Folder 115)
      Research project: "The Adoption of High Yielding Rice Varieties in Northern Thailand"
    - AS 8917 - Khin Win, U, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 116)
    - AS 8917 - Khin Win, U: Supplementary Material (Box 20, Folder 117, Box 21, Folder 118)
    - AS 8918 - Brown University - "Overcoming Hunger in the 1990s" Conference, 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 119)
    - AS 8925 - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) - Workshop on Methodology for Rice-Soil Physical Measurements Relevant to Sustainable Crop Production in Resource-Poor Regions, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 120)
      Workshop jointly organized by the Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) and IRRI
    - AS 8926 - Takavarasha, Tobias, 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 121)
      Research topic: Agricultural pricing policy in Zimbabwe
    - AS 8928 - Lu, Qingshan, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 122)
      Research topic: Sorghum research
    - AS 8929 - Institute of Fundamental Studies, Sri Lanka - International Symposium on Rice Production on Acid Soils of the Tropics, 1988-1990 (Box 21, Folder 123)
    - AS 8931 - Bangladesh Institute of Development Studies - Library Development, 1989, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 124)
    - AS 8932 - Hedges, Trevor Richard, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 125)
    - AS 8933 - University of Illinois - Soybean Conference, 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 126)